(Penny:)we just leave things
the way they are,
(Sheldon:)and...
(Penny:)sometimes we'll sleep
over there,
(Penny:)and sometimes
we'll sleep over here.
(Sheldon:)But mostly here.
(Bernadette:)Sure.
W-W-What about what you
said in the restaurant?
(Penny:)Well, it's not forever.
(Penny:)It's just for a while.
(Penny:)If you want, we can think of him
like he's our dog.
(Penny:)You can.
(Sheldon:)I'm happy when you come home.
(Sheldon:)And I'm scared of fireworks.
And by the way, on July Fourth,
we're all sleeping here.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
All right, great!
(Sheldon:)Just give me one minute,
(Sheldon:)and I'll get started
on a new Roommate Agreement.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Nothing from Pratt. We're good.
♪ Indy's whip snapped ♪
♪ Thor's hammer missed ♪
♪ It was Avenger ♪
♪ Versus archeologist ♪